And ken just seems kind of angry.
And that's what you missed on...
♪ glee. ♪
I bet we get stuck with mr. Sinacori
As our sectionals advisor.
Oh, the creepy math teacher?
He's always singing when he walks down the halls.
Hey, guys.
Did any of you think it was weird
The way that puck rushed to quinn's aid
During rehearsal yesterday?
Is it the baby?
Is it coming?
Think we're supposed to get hot towels.
Would you both just shut up!
There's, like, sweat on the floor. I slipped, okay?
I'm fine!
No.
I mean, he likes her.
I mean, they're friends.
We all know that.
Rachel:
Yeah, but it seemed like more than that.
I've never told you guys this before,
But I'm a little psychic.
I can't read minds or anything yet,
But I do have a sixth sense.
Something is definitely going on there.
Uh, we... We got to go.
We have to practice.
Oh, and we will, as soon as mr. Schuester
Names a faculty advisor to replace him.
There's nothing to be scared of.
I mean, it... It's not like carrie or anything.
(school bell ringing)
Hey. She's onto it.
I know. It's really freaking me out.
Hold up.
(phone vibrating)
Artie's buzzing in.
I'm going party line.
Dudes, this is serious.
If she finds out, she's going to tell finn.
She's a total trout mouth.
Kurt wants in.
I say we lock rachel up until after sectionals.
I volunteer my basement.
We can't.
We need her to sing.
Damn her talent.
We just heard.
Who told?
We assumed it was you.
Why would
I do that?
To get back at puck.
Aren't you guys dating?
Sex is not dating.
If it were, santana and I would be dating.
Look, I don't want to rock the boat.
Since quinn got pregnant,
I'm top dog around here.
Hold up.
Rachel's walking by.
Hey, hot mama?
She's gone.
Look, I know
I screwed up
Telling all you guys about quinn and puck,
And I feel really terrible about it,
But we cannot let rachel figure this out.
If she tells finn, he's going to flip.
And then, we really have no chance at sectionals.
Sync by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com
Are you sure about this?
But the wedding is on Saturday.
Your wedding.
I know.
We just pushed it back a few hours.
Now it doesn't have to happen in broad daylight.
Really, I want to do this, will.
I want to take the kids to sectionals.
Okay, but... What about ken?
I mean, he-he's going to be furious.
I appealed to him as an educator.
You will always choose schuester over me.
He won't even be there, ken.
I am doing this for the kids.
I really thought
That you of all people would understand this.
This time,
I don't think that I do.
He took it great.
Just great.
(laughs)
I can't thank you enough.
(school bell rings)
Rachel:
Hey.
I know it's not my place, but have you had your doctor run
The full genetic test panel on your unborn child?
I only ask
Because my cousin, leon, and his wife got pregnant,
And then they found out that he was a carrier for tay-sachs.
What's that?
It's a genetic disorder--
Pretty terrible from what I understand.
If one of the parents is a carrier,
Then there's, like, a 50% chance that the child has it
Or something like that.
No, leon's... Leon's baby was fine.
(stammering): It was still pretty scary, though.
My doctor never mentioned that.
You know... I'm such an idiot.
They would only run the test if one of the parents was jewish.
Yeah, only jews carry the gene.
Oh.
Okay, I'll see you in rehearsal.
(school bell ringing)
You have to take me to go get those jewish baby tests.
Why? Is that even a real thing?
Because, if something is wrong with the baby,
Terri schuester isn't going to take it.
And I can't ask finn.
He'll know something's up.
Does this have to happen tonight?
Because I have my fight club.
Will:
Hey, guys?
Let's, uh... Let's gather 'round.
Well... I have found my replacement.
So, give it up for ms. Pillsbury.
(sparse applause)
She's the one they made me talk to
When they found out I was keeping that bird in my locker.
So, do you even know anything about music?
Well...
What's important
Is that she cares about you guys
Every bit as much as I do.
Now...
(sighs)
I-I don't know what the future holds for me...
And for us, but I know, Saturday,
You're going to make me proud.
You guys are going to be great.
So...
Good-bye for now.
Wait.
What about our set list?
I... I can't help you with that.
You've got to figure that out for yourselves.
All right, guys.
Well, we have to do "proud mary" in wheelchairs. That's in.
And "don't stop believing," for sure.
What about the ballad?
I would be thrilled
To contribute a ballad from my repertoire.
Mercedes:
Okay, you know what, miss bossy pants?
Enough.
I've worked just as hard as you, and I'm just as good as you.
You know, you always end up stealing the spotlight.
Mercedes, do you honestly think
You're as strong of a balladeer as I am?
(whispering):
Ballads are kind of my thing.
Emma:
Okay, um, rachel,
Why don't you let mercedes
Give it a try?
Thanks, mrs. P.
Emma:
Okay.
Rachel.
Do I even need to tell you what song?
Horns, strings, keep up.
♪ and I am telling you ♪
♪ I'm not going ♪
♪ you're the best man
I'll ever know ♪
♪ there's no way I can ever go ♪
♪ no, no, there's no way ♪
♪ no, no, no, no way
I'm living without you ♪
♪ I'm not living without you ♪
♪ I don't want to be free ♪
♪ I'm staying ♪
♪ and you, and you ♪
♪ you're going to love me ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ tear down the mountains ♪
♪ yell, scream and shout ♪
♪ you can say what you want,
I'm not walking out ♪
♪ stop all the rivers ♪
♪ push, strike and kill ♪
♪ I'm not going to leave you ♪
♪ there's no way I will ♪
♪ and I am ♪
♪ telling you ♪
♪ I'm not going ♪
♪ I'm not living without you ♪
♪ not living without you ♪
♪ I don't want to be free ♪
♪ I'm staying, I'm staying ♪
♪ and you, and you, and you ♪
♪ you're going to love me... ♪
♪ yeah.... Yeah! ♪
♪ love me, love me ♪
♪ love... ♪
♪ me! ♪
(cheering and applause)
Thoughts?
It's clear the room adores you.
And, although it wouldn't be my first choice, well...
I can't wait to see you sing that song at sectionals.
You're amazing, mercedes, and you deserve it.
I'm going to hug you now.
Okay. Come on.
(laughing)
(school bell ringing)
That was pretty cool in there.
I... I know that must have been hard for you.
It was the right thing to do.
I... I wanted to bring the team together.
Yeah.
You know,
I got to be honest.
I'm kind of pumped about sectionals.
This has been a...
Hard couple of months-- with quinn and the baby
And everything and...
I don't know--
I really think that...
Winning could make everything good for while.
You know?
Is that stupid?
It's not stupid at all.
Is something up with you?
I want you to be happy, finn.
Oh.
And when you care about someone,
You can't sit around and watch them suffer
When you know you can do something about it.
What are you talking about?
I have to tell you something.
(grunting and groaning)
Hey, come on, come on.
Get off him!
Knock it off! Get off! Get off!
Hey.
Tell the truth!
Punk just walked in and sucker punched me.
Don't play dumb-- you're too freaking dumb to play dumb.
Will:
Come on!
Who told you this, finn?
Obviously, it was rachel.
What? I didn't do anything.
Yeah, it was rachel, but I want to hear it from you.
I want to heart it from both of you.
Finn, just calm down.
No! They're both lying to me!
Is it true?
Just tell me-- is it true?
Yes.
Puck is the father.
(stammers)
So, all...
All that stuff in the hot tub...
You just made that up?
You were stupid enough to buy it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
(sobbing):
I am so sorry.
Screw this.
I'm done with you.
I'm done with...
I'm done with all of you!
(chair clattering)
(school bell ringing)
I'm so sorry.
I fully understand if you want to beat me up.
If you can, just try to avoid my nose.
I'm not mad at you.
All you did was what I wasn't brave enough to do--
Tell the truth.
I was selfish when I told him.
I wanted to break you two up,
So he would want to be with me.
And now neither of us have him.
I have hurt so many people.
Can you go now?
I just really want to be alone.
Hey.
(sniffling)
So, I know you're upset now.
But I want to be with you.
And I'm going to do everything I can
To be a good dad to our baby.
Thanks.
But I honestly can't handle
Any more stress in my life right now.
I'm going to do this on my own.
I know you don't understand it.
But please respect it.
(mechanical whirring)
So, the competition starts at 11:00.
Right.
I'll have my cell phone on.
I know. You already told me.
Three times.
And you wrote it down.
Reporting for duty,
Mr. Schuester.
I have to tell you,
I get terrible public event anxiety.
You know what, jacob?
It's okay. We just need a 12th member.
All right, so, um, just sway in back.
You don't even have to sing.
Yeah, don't even sing.
Okay.
Great.
(under breath): God.
So, um, still no word from finn?
No.
I can't thank you enough.
Okay.
Emma: Okay.
So, smooth sailing so far, we're all signed in.
And, um...
...According to the program,
You have drawn performance slot number three.
We're going last?
Isn't that bad?
Hardly.
This is good news.
My extensive auditioning for community theater has taught me
That we either want to go first or last.
If we're first, then everyone has to measure up to us,
And if we're last,
Then we're freshest in the judges' minds.
And did you ever get any of those parts?
I'm with rachel. On this.
The glass is definitely half full
Of some very good things right now.
Yeah, ms. Pillsbury's right.
I mean, we're here now, right?
No reason not
To go in with some positive mojo.
Right. Right.
Right.
♪ and you, and you ♪
♪ and you ♪
♪ you're gonna love me ♪
(holding note)
♪ you're gonna love ♪ it's a really popular song.
♪ me! ♪
(cheering, applause)
♪ rolling, rolling ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ rolling on the river... ♪
Emma:
We've got a problem.
They're doing all of our numbers.
The kids are completely freaking out.
Artie keeps ramming himself into the wall,
And I'm pretty sure jacob ben israel wet himself.
I knew it!
Sue leaked the set list.
Will...
Will, these kids need a leader right now.
Just hold tight.
I know what to do.
Okay.
Sue!
What kind of teacher are you?
Hey, buddy! I just came by to feed my venus flytrap.
You leaked the set list!
And you are not going to get away with it!
That is a libelous accusation,
And I insist you retract it immediately.
You have no proof.
No proof?
You are the only person who had the list!
But other than that, you have no proof.
It's time to face facts, william.
At 1:00 p.M. This afternoon,
Your little club will have had its shot at the big time,
And they will have failed.
Glee club will be canceled,
And all that money figgins has been funneling
Into your budget will finally
And rightfully be restored to mine.
You have crossed the line.
I am not going to sit idly by anymore.
I am going to expose you
For the fraud that you have become.
Bring it on, william.
I'm reasonably confident
That you will be adding revenge
To the long list of things you're no good at--
Right next to being being married...
Don't.
...Running a high school glee club,
And finding a hairstyle
That doesn't make you look like a lesbian.
Love ya like a sista.
Get your hands off me.
You're not going to push a woman, are you?
I didn't think so.
Hey, finn.
I just called your mom.
She told me you'd be here.
Yeah, you know, football season ended,
So I'm just cleaning out my things.
Sounds like something that could've waited till Monday.
You heard anything?
Yeah.
It's pretty bad.
I can't be there.
And I can?
I can't even
Be in the same room as her without crying like a girl.
I can't look at him without wanting to punch his face off.
I don't have any more pep talks, finn.
You know I know how you feel.
All I know is that--
Between you and me--
I don't think that they can win without you.
But that's not fair.
Why does it always have to come down to me?
Why do I always have to be the bigger man?
Because sometimes being special...
Sucks.
I just want everything to be like it--
Like it never happened, you know?
Well, finn...
...You can't always get what you want.
Listen, I'll be in the choir room.
Oh, mr. Shue, you forgot your keys.
No, I didn't.
Nope, your money's no good here,
I'm buying.
Celebratory giant pretzels.
I don't feel much like celebrating.
Why not?
One of us is going to take this thing.
Hi.
Nice set list.
Of course, I haven't heard your deaf kids perform yet,
But I hear they're doing
"don't stop believing."
Um, who are you?
I'm so sorry, let me introduce myself.
I'm emma pillsbury.
I'm the faculty advisor for the mckinley high school glee club.
Oh. What happened to the white guy with the jheri curl?
You should be ashamed.
Aren't you ashamed?
You're educators.
Actually, no, you know what?
You're more than that.
You take care of disadvantaged kids.
And you're teaching them that
The only way they can compete in this world is by cheating.
I'm sorry, but what kind of message is that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
"don't stop believing" is the most downloaded song
In the history of itunes.
I've only got one good ear
And even I know that.
Scarlet fever.
Right, and "proud mary?"
In wheelchairs?
Do you have any idea
How much winning is going to mean to my girls?
It's going to be a life changer--
Make them feel like they're worth something again.
I'm-I'm sorry, do you-- do you think
That they're not going to know that something's up?
The fact that you just magically came up
With two brand-new numbers days before competition?
They were great up there.
That's all I know.
I think
What we have here is a case of deaf racism.
Shame on you.
No, you know what the real shame is?
Is that maybe if you believed in them just a little bit more
They would've been amazing up there.
Without cheating.
♪ ♪
♪ don't stop believing ♪
♪ hold on to that feeling ♪
♪ streetlight people ♪
(holding note)
Meeting in the green room in five minutes.
♪ don't stop believing... ♪
You leaked the set list, you don't want to be here--
You were just sue sylvester's little moles.
I know for a fact that's true.
Sue asked us to spy for her.
Santana:
Look, we may still be cheerios,
But neither of us ever gave sue the set list.
Well... I-I did, but I didn't know
What she was going to do with it.
Okay, look, believe what you want,
But no one's forcing me to be here.
And if you ever tell anyone this I'll deny it--
But I like being in glee club.
It's the best part of my day, okay?
I wasn't going to go and mess it up.
I believe you.
Okay, look, guys, there's no point in us arguing anymore.
We-we have go on in an hour.
And we have no songs.
Perhaps I could improvise some of my def poetry jams.
No.
No?
Look, we're going to do this the right way.
Let's start with the ballad.
Mercedes, do you have anything else in your repertoire?
Yeah, but it's not as good
As anything you're going to sing.
No, we, we agreed...
We agreed
That I would sing
"and I'm telling you,"
And that ain't happening.
Look, rachel,
The truth is you're the best singer that we've got.
Kurt:
As much as it hurts me to admit it-- and it does--
She's right.
Rachel's our star.
If anyone is going
To go belt it on the fly, it should be her.
Well, I do have something
That I've been working on since I was four.
Then I guess we have our ballad, and we can close
With "somebody to love."
It's a real crowd-pleaser.
Yeah, that and a can of soup will guarantee us third place.
We still need another song
We can all sing together.
I have one.
(sighs)
I found the sheet music online.
I used the cheerios' copier to make copies
And then I trashed the thing.
Mike, matt,
Brittany, santana, you're our best dancers.
Figure something out and we'll all follow your lead.
It's going to be choppy.
Good.
We're best when we're loose.
Look, all we have going for us is that we believe in ourselves
And what we're singing about.
If we can show the judges that...
...We might have a shot at this thing.
It's good to have you back, finn.
You cool if I take my spot back?
Quite.
I was just here because I was hoping
To get into rachel's pants.
(sighs)
We cool, dude?
No.
Finn...
You okay?
Don't worry about me.
Okay, this is all up to you now.
You wanted the solo, you wanted
The chance to be the star.
This is your chance.
Don't screw it up.
(sighs)
Will:
Well, a-are they nervous?
Has it started?
Showtime.
Emcee:
And now our final team--
Mckinley high's new directions!
("don't rain on my parade" playing)
♪ don't tell me not to live ♪
♪ just sit and putter ♪
♪ life's candy and the sun's a ball of butter ♪
♪ don't bring around a cloud to rain on my parade ♪
♪ don't tell me not to fly,
I've simply got to ♪
♪ if someone takes a spill, it's me and not you ♪
♪ who told you you're allowed to rain on my ♪
♪ parade ♪
♪ I'm marching my band out ♪
♪ I'm beating my drum ♪
♪ and if I'm fanned out ♪
♪ your turn at bat, sir ♪
♪ at least I didn't fake it ♪
♪ hat, sir,
I guess I didn't make it ♪
♪ but whether I'm the rose of sheer perfection ♪
♪ a freckle on the nose of life's complexion ♪
♪ the cinder or the shiny apple ♪
♪ of its eye ♪
♪ I gotta fly once,
I gotta try once ♪
♪ only can die once ♪
♪ right, sir? ♪
♪ oh, life is juicy, juicy, and you see ♪
♪ I gotta have my bite, sir ♪
♪ get ready for me, love,
'cause I'm a comer ♪
♪ I simply gotta March, my heart's a drummer ♪
♪ don't bring around a cloud ♪
♪ to rain on my parade ♪
♪ I'm gonna live and live now ♪
♪ get what I want, I know how ♪
♪ one roll for the whole shebang ♪
♪ one throw, that bell will go clang ♪
♪ eye on the target and wham! ♪
♪ one shot, one gunshot, and bam! ♪
♪ hey, mr. Arnstein ♪
♪ here I am... ♪
♪ I'll March my band... ♪
♪ out ♪
♪ I'll beat ♪
♪ my drum ♪
♪ and if I'm fanned out ♪
♪ your turn at bat, sir ♪
♪ at least I didn't fake it, hat, sir ♪
♪ I guess I didn't make it ♪
♪ get ready for me, love ♪
♪ 'cause I'm a comer ♪
♪ I simply gotta March, my heart's a drummer ♪
♪ nobody, no, nobody ♪
♪ is gonna ♪
♪ rain on my ♪
♪ parade! ♪
Ladies and gentlemen, the new directions.
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ but if you try sometimes ♪
♪ you'll find ♪
♪ you get what you need ♪
♪ oh... ♪
♪ I saw her today ♪
♪ at the reception ♪
♪ a glass of wine ♪
♪ in her hand ♪
♪ I knew she was gonna meet ♪
♪ her connection ♪
♪ at her feet was her footloose man ♪
♪ no, you can't ♪
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ oh, no, no, you can't ♪
♪ what you want ♪
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ but if you try sometimes ♪
♪ well, you just might find ♪
♪ you get what you need ♪
Mercedes:
♪ hey, hey, yeah ♪
♪ and I went down to the demonstration ♪
♪ to get my fair share of abuse ♪
Finn & rachel:
♪ singin' we're ♪
♪ gonna vent our frustration ♪
♪ if we don't, we're gonna blow a 50-amp fuse ♪
♪ sing it to me now ♪
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ no, no, no, no ♪
Mercedes:
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ oh... ♪
♪ but if you try sometimes ♪
♪ well, you just might find ♪
♪ you get what you need ♪
Mercedes:
♪ oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ get what you need ♪
♪ you can't always get what you want ♪
♪ oh, yeah, what you need ♪
♪ what you need, yeah ♪
♪ yeah! ♪
♪ what you need! ♪
Okay, I'm just going to come out and say it.
This is a singing competition.
I don't know how those deaf kids got in.
They weren't singing.
They were, like, honking
And everyone was crying and
I was, like, "get off the stage.
You're terrible and you're making me super uncomfortable."
Now, hold on just a second, candy.
Those haverhurst kids twice had me reaching for my handkerchief,
And those jane addams girls had it going on
In all the right places.
Woman:
Can I just say something?
I have no idea what the hell I'm doing here.
I'm serious.
I don't understand what a glee club is
And I have never even heard the term "show choir"
Until about three hours ago
When my boss told me he had tickets to nascar
And I had to fill in at this fool event.
Those jane addams girls--
I'll be damned
If I didn't apportion hundreds of thousands
Of taxpayers' dollars to that school
So they can parade their behinds around like a bunch
Of hoochie hos.
The mckinley group was good but didn't seem all that rehearsed,
But I liked their energy.
Well, I have to admit
I have a soft spot
For the rolling stones.
I was at altamont speedway in '69.
I actually saw that guy get stabbed.
Can't get that image out of my noggin
To this day.
I seriously don't know
What either one of you are talking about.
I have never been so bored.
I mean,
If I had to pick a group that I hated the least...
It doesn't sound good, guys.
Hey,
Um...
I just wanted to say how great you all were,
And I thought you were amazing.
We have nothing to say to you.
Because we cheated, I know.
I feel terrible about it,
But I'm going to tell the judges right now
That we don't deserve to win.
And your e-mail addresses?
You guys were so much fun to watch.
You should be very proud.
Get me the hell out of here.
Um, excuse me, um, I have something I need to tell you.
I'm sorry, we've made our decision.
Hi.
I thought you worked on Saturday afternoon.
Yeah, I came home early.
I'm tired.
I haven't been sleeping very well.
What's with the monkey suit?
Ken and emma's wedding-- it's at 4:00.
Oh, yeah.
Here.
Oh, I'm fine.
Oh.
I want you to know
I've been seeing a therapist.
Oh, it's just at the local community center, but still.
Good.
I hope it works out for you.
I'm taking responsibility, will.
I mean, I'm weak, and I'm selfish,
And I let my anxiety rule my life,
But you know I wasn't always that way.
It's just that... I wanted so many things
That I know we're never going to have.
But that was okay as long as I still had you.
Say something?
I'm looking at you,
And I'm trying.
I mean, I really want to feel that thing
I always felt when I looked at you before.
That feeling of family,
Of love.
But it's gone.
Forever?
I don't know.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Nice ice sculpture.
Where's ken?
Um, home,
I'd imagine,
Probably trying to regain some of the pride
That I stole from him.
He dumped me.
What?
He said moving the wedding for sectionals was the last straw.
But I thought he understood
That-that you were doing this for the kids.
He understand that...
...I wasn't doing it for the kids.
I was doing it for you.
Emma...
I'm so sorry.
No. Gosh, no, it's not your fault.
I-I really messed up.
He was absolutely right.
I was settling for him.
Really, one blink from you, will,
And I would have been out the door.
So, um...
I e-mailed my resignation to figgins.
I...
My last day is Monday.
I just can't...
(crying)
I just can't be at that school.
I can't see ken without feeling ashamed,
And I can't see you without feeling heartbroken.
I just left my wife.
No.
I'm sorry. I, um...
I'm going.
But I just...
Just left your wife.
Exactly.
You just did.
You make a beautiful bride.
Thank you.
(door closes)
Sue, the directors, both from the jane addams academy
And haverbrook school for the deaf,
Have informed me
That you gave them the new directions' set list.
You have no proof.
The set lists were on cheerios' letterhead.
I didn't do it.
They say, "from the desk of sue sylvester."
Circumstantial evidence.
They're written in your handwriting!
Forgeries.
Sue, there is an orgy of evidence stacked against you!
Well, you've clearly made up your mind not
To be impartial in this case.
So let's see if you can't wrap up this little lecture,
Slap me on the wrist, and let me get back
To whipping my squad of champions into shape.
We have to be in albuquerque
In a couple of weeks for nationals.
Sue!
Sit down!
Sue, as of today,
You are no longer coach of the cheerios.
I beg your pardon?
As of today,
You are no longer coach of the cheerios.
(gasps)
I beg your pardon!
All this time,
I thought...
I beg your pardon?!
All this time, I thought mr.
Schuester was overreacting.
And frankly, I was too willing
To look past your monkeyshines because you kept winning.
But now, you've gone too far!
You have embarrassed yourself
And besmirched the name of william mckinley.
A failed president.
Oh, please!
The greatest one who ever lived!
You are suspended from this school as of today.
Shue, you have anything to add?
I think you said it all.
My word is official!
Let it be written.
Okay, if this is the way you want to play it.
Okay.
Shue, in light of sue's interference,
I am reinstating you as coach of the glee club.
I contacted the ohio show choir governing board
And set the record straight.
Thank you, sir.
My pleasure.
(sighs) all right.
Good job.
(school bell ringing)
(laughs)
Schuester?
Well played, sir.
I underestimated you.
All right, here's what happens.
I'm gonna head down to my condo in boca to brown up a bit,
Get myself back into fighting shape.
Then I'm gonna return to this school
Even more hell-bent on your destruction.
Get ready for the ride of your life, will schuester.
You are about to board the sue sylvester express.
Destination? Horror!
I look forward to it, sue.
You know you just woke a sleeping giant.
Prepared to be crushed.
(sighs)
Hmm.
Well, we have a few things we'd like to show you, mr. Shue.
The first...
(students shouting, will laughing)
(applause) wow!
(laughs) yeah!
I am so proud of you guys.
You won fair and square.
The result was unanimous,
And the judges didn't even know about all the shenanigans
That were going on behind the scenes.
So... Congratulations.
You earned this.
(whooping, cheering and applause) yeah!
Give it up!
Come on! All right!
But...
...Now we have regionals to worry about.
And you can bet that vocal adrenaline
Is hard at work, so we should be, too.
So, let's get started.
Uh, wait, mr. Shue.
There's one more thing.
Since you weren't able to be there to see us perform,
We put together a special number just for you.
♪ take a seat! ♪
(laughter)
♪ la, la-la, la, la, la ♪
♪ la, la-la, la, la ♪
♪ guess this means you're sorry, you're standing at my door ♪
♪ guess this means you take back all you said before ♪
♪ like how much you wanted anyone but me ♪
♪ said you'd never come back, but here you are again ♪
♪ 'cause we belong together now, yeah ♪
♪ forever united here somehow, yeah ♪
♪ you got a piece of me ♪
♪ and honestly ♪
♪ my life ♪
♪ would suck ♪
♪ without you ♪
♪ you know that
I've got issues ♪
♪ but you're pretty messed up, too ♪
♪ either way, I found out
I'm nothing without you ♪
♪ 'cause we belong together now ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ forever united here somehow, yeah ♪
♪ you got a piece of me ♪
♪ and honestly ♪
♪ my life ♪
♪ would suck ♪
♪ without you ♪
♪ 'cause we belong together now ♪
♪ together now ♪
♪ forever united here somehow, yeah ♪
♪ you got a piece of me ♪
♪ and honestly ♪
What?
♪ my life ♪
♪ would suck ♪
♪ without you! ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com